カイト救出を誓った ゴンとキルア
He knows exactly what we're doing.
だが　ＮＧＬに戻るには
We won't be able to trick him.
討伐隊を率いる ネテロ会長から出された
What I felt after coming into
contact with your Nen
ある条件をクリアしなければ ならなかった
was not anger, fear, or hatred.
何？　それ。
Only senses of duty and resolve.
割り符だよ 印のついた竹や木の板切れを ２つに割って　互いに持つんだ。
If you are fighting for the survival
of humanity, your battle is over.
これで仲間の証しや 文書の証明にしたりする。
You need further explanation? It seems you doubt what you've just heard.
((最寄りの街に２人 刺客を放った))
Then I shall repeat myself. You have won... The battle is over.
今回の場合は　刺客が　それぞれ 片方の割り符を持っている。
The rest of what I have to
say is for your ears only.
倒して奪えってことだな。
The reason I am here is quite simple.
消されてる。
That is really all I want.
確認したってことだよな。
I desire nothing else.
うん。
After coming into contact with your Nen, I learned my current state and fate.
あなた達が　キルアとゴンね。
And having learned my fate, I simply wish
はじめまして。
to spend my remaining time with Komugi.
私　パームって者です。
That is all I want.
説明するわ お茶でも飲みましょう。
Was this...
私は　ノヴ先生の弟子なの。
Was this a plan you devised after
discovering my personality?
先生には 足手まといだって言われたけど
No, I already know the answer... It's impossible. You expect me to believe you?
無理やり　ついて来たの。 誰？
You think I'll just accept that explanation?!
多分 ネテロ会長と　一緒にいた人だ。 そうそう　黒スーツの…。
An omnipotent King would
never lie to himself in order to fool a lower being like me!
先生って素晴らしい人よ。 クールで　知的で　冷静で。
After all the killing you have done,
and soon will do...
あっ　冷静は　クールと同じ意味ね やだわ。
A creature like you... The King admits defeat? Cares for a human?
あっ　でも　尊敬してるだけよ。
Impossible! That's impossible!
別に恋愛感情は…
He's doing this because it is the truth!
ない… とは言い切れないかも　ウフフ…。
I believe it was only a slight change...
だって　大切だものね。
Huh?
相手を尊敬できるかどうかって 恋愛に。 あっ　もちろん こんなこと　先生は知らないわよ。
Something, somewhere, changed ever so slightly.
何も言ってないし…　これからも。 うわぁ…
In my current state, I am not a god, but I... No...
ゲフっ。 分からないわよね 先のことなんて。 だって　だって　恋愛って
Perhaps, I only feel this way
because everything has fallen into place.
突然　発展するものじゃない？ そう思わない？
You should know I have very little time.
えと　ちょっと　いい？ 俺達　戦うんだよね？
I want you to tell me her location, so I do not have to search for her.
えっ　あっ　やだわ そうよね　ごめんなさい。 会長と先生に
What are you saying?! Stop this... Yes, I know where she is!
これ以上の同伴は 絶対ダメって言われて。
Why don't you just torture it out of me? I know the answer.
でも　私　食い下がったの 絶対行くって。
We both know that isn't an option.
一生分　話したんじゃないか ってぐらい 自分の熱意をアピールしたわ。 そしたら　条件付きで 許してくれたの　フフフ…。
Your aura is as strong and beautiful
as any I have ever beheld. Stop this!
いや　だから…。 先生ね　冷たく見えるけど ホントは　とても優しいのよ。
All I can do is to ask you to help me.
あの２人　下品で野蛮で 口のきき方も知らない クソガキどもが
I am part Ant now...
私を差し置いて ＮＧＬに行くなんて 許せる？　いや無理。 うわ！ パームさん！　「発」止めて　「発」！
I know very well how important
you are to the race...
この人　俺と同じ強化系だ 何か　やだな…
Not that...
ナックルとシュート？ 俺達じゃなくて？
Don't go to such lengths...
そうよ。 だって　ナックルとシュートを 倒すのは　私じゃなくて
You mustn't do that... I'll tell you.
あなた達だから。
But on one condition.
ナックルとシュートは モラウさんの弟子よ。
May I use my power
内容は分からないけど　とにかく
to watch your final moments with her?
ＮＧＬに行けるのは 私達か彼らか どちらか　ひと組だけ。
If that is what it takes to be with Komugi, you certainly may.
１か月間 割り符を手放すなってことは
Sorry, Killua...
誰かが奪いに来るってことだ。
I couldn't keep our promise...
男子たるもの　敵に 背を向けたりするんじゃねえぞ！
4-7-1, marshal...
まっ　場所が分かっても 行かないけど
Wake up, Komugi.
ありゃ　おとりだな　もう１人が どこかで見張ってるはずだ
It's time to play.
パームの話だと　相手は　俺達の 名前すら知らないらしいからな。 うん。
We have a shocking news update.
何とかして俺達を あぶり出す気だろう。
The true purpose of the summoning
本気で　あんなことするバカは いないよ。 そいつ　強そうだった？
of all Republic of East Gorteau
citizens to the capital city
かなりな。
was a plot by the Supreme
Leader to massacre them.
どのくらいで倒せると思う？ そりゃ分かんねえよ。
The body of Supreme Leader Diego
was discovered under the rubble, suggesting that the victims were
likely forced into mass suicide.
会長の連れにも言われたけど 「念」の戦いに絶対なんてないしな。 ただ　そいつに言わせると 俺の勝ち目って考え方が ズレてるらしいけど
But the second-in-command,
Secretary Bizeff, is still missing, so some authorities believe a
revolution is the greater likelihood.
俺は　そうは思わない。
Meanwhile, there has also been trouble
勝つ確率を上げなきゃ 生き残れるわけがないんだ。
in the NGL region of the Mitene Union,
as international peacekeepers
相手と自分との力量を測るのは 重要な作業だ。
have sent queries regarding refugees, and have received no response.
仮に１００回　戦ったとして １２回しか勝てないんじゃ
There have been rumors of
論外だからな。
illicit dealings between
East Gorteau and NGL, and the international community
seeks to use this incident
最低でも５割。 できれば７割以上の勝算が欲しい。
as an opportunity to conduct
a more forceful investigation.
そのために俺達が しなきゃならないことは　２つ。
Yeah, the boss did his duty.
少しでも基礎能力を上げることと 相手の能力を知ること。 うん。
No, I wasn't there to see it.
相手の能力さえ分かれば
It still isn't clear yet.
ゲンスルーの時みたく 対策が立てやすい。 うん…。
Yeah, we're waiting on Palm.
半分賛成　半分反対。
Can we really trust her alone to verify the King's death?
どういうことだ？ 基礎能力を上げるのは　俺も賛成。
Plus, that person was captured and converted by the enemy, yes?
でも　相手の能力は 知らなくていいと思う。
Well, that's a question of professionalism.
はぁ？　何でだよ？
It would be professional
それじゃ　リスクが高くなるだけで 何もいいこと　ねえだろ。
to provide a complete report
in the safest manner possible.
でも　それが普通でしょ ＮＧＬでの戦いはさ。
But those are the professionals who spend all of their time sitting in fully-furnished offices.
俺達の目的は　ナックル達を 倒すことじゃなくて
And when we field Hunters are told
to trust a partner, we trust them.
強くなってＮＧＬに戻り カイトを助けること。
We're all professionals... But I'm the one out in the field!
つまり　どんな敵か 分からない状況で戦っても 勝てるっていう強さがいるんだ。
The Vice Chairman's faction won't
accept that argument.
下準備が必要な勝ち方なんて 意味ないよ。
If they find out, you can expect
to be questioned, at the least.
なっ！ どわ！ バカか　お前は！ あっ！ あっ！
Uh, I am Netero...
ビスケ！ ふむ。 何で　ここに？
Chairman, thank you for a job well done.
私が呼んだの。 えっ？　まさか知り合い？ えっ？　まさか知り合い？
May you rest in peace.
いいえ　あなた達のこと 調べただけよ。 どうやって？ だって　ビスケとは…。
The same day, a video was streamed
online in which Netero announced
フフフ…　私の能力を使えば 容易なことよ。 さぁ　時間が惜しいわ 開始しましょう。
his resignation as Chairman
of the Hunter Association, and gave instructions for
choosing his successor.
モラウの厮徒抹殺計画。 イヤです。 イヤです。
However, major news stories in the
government-run media overshadowed it, and only a few realized that
the video was his will.
それじゃあ　始めようか。 オス！
Now, let us drink.
痛っ！　何すんのさ　いきなり！
Let us drink.
さっきの続きだよ バカか　お前は！
Drink to the human race.
あのジジイはね 人が悪いんで有名なんだわさ。 )
In every age, there will be good
humans and bad humans.
あいつが １か月でやれっていうのは 本当なら　１年かけても 達成困難なことだったりするの！ １週間で 何とかなるわけないでしょ！
Human life is too long
to devote to reproduction, yet too short to devote to learning,
in the helix of time.
でも俺達は　一刻も早く戻って カイトを助けなきゃいけないんだ。 何の話だい？　それ。
Perhaps that is why humans succumb
to desire and seek release.
楽しかったねぇ。
Despite the fact that life is complete
with the sun, the land, and poetry.
もう一度したいなぁ…。
It's over...
さすが　年の功… 説教慣れしてやがる 分かったかい？ オス…。
But it feels like we
haven't played in ages...
んじゃ　特訓開始だわさ。
Playing in real life is completely different
than playing in my dreams.
まずは…　「練」！
Yes. I thought I felt someone kick
me hard in the stomach.
その状態を３時間　維持すること。
After that, a strange person kidnapped me...
キルア　どのくらい　いける？
But you must have saved me, Supreme Leader.
調子がいい時で 最高５５分くらいかな。
It wasn't me. It was my subordinates.
これが　できなきゃ 次には進まない。
I was wrong?!
死ぬ気でやんなさいな　ホホホ…。
I jumped to the wrong conclusion. I was unworthy of their loyalty...
ハァ…　うっ　うぅ…。
When they stop by, I must thank them.
ハァ　ハァ…。
I will relay your gratitude.
ぐっ…。
I'll be seeing them soon...
何だい １時間も　たってないわよさ。 はいはい　続けて！
I know. Let's begin.
くっ…！
Yes!
うぅ…　くっ…。
Once, you asked my name.
「練」を１０分間延ばすだけでも １か月かかるっていわれるのよ。
Y-Yes... My name is Meruem.
寝てる暇なんか ありゃしないわさ。
Meruem.
おのれ！
Meruem-sama?
臆したか　腰抜けが！ てめぇら　死刑確定！
M-My name is Komugi... It is an honor to know you!
首輪してるじゃねえかよ どこだ　飼い主はよ。 公園はキレイに使わなきゃ ダメじゃねえか　まったく…。
I knew nothing. I didn't understand what really mattered.
明日は　３０分後スタートよ！
No honorific is necessary. Don't make me repeat myself!
ようやく　私の力が 必要となる時が来たわね。
I would never dare address
you without an honorific! Then if I beat you at Gungi, you will
address me without the honorific.
さぁ　頼むわさ　クッキィちゃん！
There is no need for you to die. I am not the same person I was before.
「まじかるエステ」！
You should be prepared to lose. Yes!
「ピアノマッサージ」。
What do you want if you win?
フフっ。
I would like another match!
こんなこと言うの失礼ですけど やり方は　お任せします。
It was a foolish question. Let's begin, then.
あなたは　私の力が選んだ 答えなのだから。
1-5-1, marshal.
でも もしも１か月で　この２人が
9-9-1, marshal.
モラウの厮徒を倒すことが できなかったら
7-9-1, pawn.
私…　自分を抑える自信が ありません。
2-3-1, pawn.
私は　どうしても ＮＧＬに行きたいのです。
2-7-2, musketeer.
ホントなら　今すぐにでも。
Could it be?
それなのに　我慢して　我慢して 我慢して　我慢して
7-1-2, fortress.
我慢した揚げ句　ダメだったら…。
This is... Marshal ...kokoriko?
きっと　あなた達を殺すわ。 それ　脅し？
Komugi, do you mean to mock me?
いいえ　忠告です あなた達が心配なの。
No. I want a sincere answer. I will not allow you to fool around.
だから　もし　ダメだと思うなら 早めに　ここから 立ち去ってほしいの。
Yes, I have never fooled around
while playing Gungi.
そのほうが　今までの経験上 私の怒りは少なくて済むわ。 それって　私に言うのは　お門違い。
Very well. If you lose, you will die.
その子達が起きたら 言ってあげなさいな。
Yes.
大丈夫！　任せといて！
Is she saying this will not
mean her certain death?
絶対　パームさんを ＮＧＬに連れて行くから！
She had a number of other options.
だから　パームさんも 気づいたことがあったら
But all would only serve to lengthen the
どんどん教えてね　頑張るよ！
game without increasing her chances.
ああいう子よ　信じてあげて。
9-2-1, new lieutenant general.
これからの１か月 会長達は何する気？　ねぇ！
4-6-2, spy.
えっ？　あっ　えっと…。 「探り」と「削り」って 言ってましたね。
Th-This is...
王が生まれるまでの タイムリミットについては
She
専門家の間でも 意見が分かれるところなので…。 最短で　あと２か月という 見解に合わせて
has found a way out. That night, I realized something. Quiet!
行動して行くそうです。
Let me think.
あいつ　わしより強くねぇ？
Here. This is the only way to go!
会長より強いですって？ ご冗談を。
I should be able to checkmate her!
それが本当なら ハンターは　誰一人
When she's forced closer to my position,
my advantage grows with each move.
太刀打ちできない 道理になってしまう。 ホッ　わしが念使いで 最強だったのは 半世紀以上も昔の話じゃよ。
But if she slows down and allows
me a turn to attack, she can't stop the knight
and lieutenant general!
今じゃ　お主らと
2-6-1, knight!
どっこいどっこいといった ところじゃろう。
I reversed her new move!
それならば　十分にお強い。
What now?
全盛期の半分以下かも しれんのにか？
What is wrong?
年は　とりたくないのう。
Why do you cry?
口の減らない人だ。
Am I...
でも　やるんでしょ？
Am I allowed
できれば　御免被りたいがな。
to be so happy?
やらずに済めば それに越したことはない。
Can...
わしらの標的は 女王のみじゃからな。 まっ　あの「円」の監視を かいくぐるのは　至難。
Can so many wonderful things happen to someone like me?
問題は　いかにして 勝つかじゃが…。 妙案があれば　賜りたいのう。
I suppose I must tell you the truth. I...
まったく　人が悪い。 答えは　私達を呼んだ時点で 出ているんでしょ？
I have been poisoned, and I have little time. Meruem-sama...
静かに　１匹ずつ 消して行きましょう。
Komugi, I wanted... to spend my final moments
playing against you.
まぁ　じっくり行きましょうや。
Meruem-sama...
どうせやるなら　楽しまなきゃな。
Right now, I am very happy.
さて　まずは　敵の数ぐらいは 知らなきゃな。 行け！
I may not be worthy, but please allow me to join you.
うん？
I see...
大勢だ　何か来る
I believe
生物じゃないな 敵の力かな？
that I was born to be here today.
さて　どうするかニャ 待ってて構わないだろう ニャ？
...was born for this moment.
あの夢のような時間を…)) )
4-4-1, pawn.
)
6-5-1, knight. 2-7-2, new spy.
ダハ！
Komugi, are you still there? Yes, I sure am.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
I'm not going anywhere.
ほらほら　何やってんの！ そんなんじゃ キメラアントどころか
4-5-1, lieutenant general.
ナックルとシュートにも 勝てやしないよ。
That's checkmate.
ＮＧＬ行きは　諦めるのかい？
Komugi, are you still here?
誰が…
Yes, yes... Right here.
諦めるか！
Let's play another match. The loser goes first.
俺達は　どんなことをしたって
Komugi... Yes, yes? What is it?
ＮＧＬに 戻らなきゃならないんだ！ うお！ うお！
It appears I never defeated
you a single time.
カイトを助けるために！
We've just gotten started! Yes...
再会したビスケによって 再び始まった修行の日々
1-5-1, marshal. 9-5-1, marshal.
目的は　ただ一つ
Komugi, are you still here?
カイトを助けるために 強くなること
Yes, of course.
その強い思いが ゴンを突き動かしていた
It's your turn, Meruem-sama. I'm a little tired...